[{"answer": "\"Meet the Fockers.\"", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 6, "question": "Probably -- one of the \"Night at the Museum\" maybe?", "qSentId": 5}, {"answer": "I think there's an advantage because you know what you're going into.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Advantage or disadvantage?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "I feel like we've inherited a bad situation over the last eight years and Obama is in a very tough position.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "What's going on with your country?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "Whoo!", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "You hate doing these things, don't you?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "I mean, it's not really you.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "What is the idea of me?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "I like doing that.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Piers, when did it begin, the need to delve deep into people's souls?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "And, actually, you like doing it.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Do you like the pressure of having to be funny?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Not \"Envy,\" I know that.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "Do you know which of your 30 movies has grossed the most?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Oh, gosh, there's more than three.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "What are your three worst movies?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "TILLER: Oh, in terms of money, I'd probably like -- you like that movie.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "What's been the biggest turkey of your life?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "\"Meet the Fockers.\"", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Probably one of the -- \"The Night at the Museum,\" maybe?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "What did you do, Focker?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "That's because it's from Debbie's left breast, Greg.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "What's the sign for sour milk?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "It tells you about anything.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "What does that tell you about our culture?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "At first, it was pretty intimidating because I'm such a fan of his, and his movies from my generation growing up are so iconic.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "What was it like working with De Niro?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Well, it depends what you're talking about.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Advantage or disadvantage?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean, at first, what I meant was I can see how having parents who are in the business can be helpful, advice and everything else.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "But then there's also -- then you have to kind of make your own way and, you know?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "My dad's a pretty hardworking guy.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "What values did they instill in you, do you think?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "No, that's not true.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "Well, they -- I have -- personally, they're not that interested in watching my -- I'm not going to try to get them to watch, you know, something about marriage and like that, because they're 9 and 6.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Are there some you don't let them watch?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "TILLER: They are -- they're very theatrical children.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Are they showing signs of comedic genius?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I love being a father, yes.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Do you like being a father?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "You have to figure out how you're going to do it so that you make sure that you have the family time.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Yes, I mean, in terms of your filming schedule, how do you juggle that with being a dad?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "I think it's -- I think it's a tough business.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "Yes, what do you really think of it?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "The dream's hollow and empty, yes.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Is the dream what you hoped it would be?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Hollow and empty and cold.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "They can be.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Are they?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Present company exempted?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "It's well hidden.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "There's no evidence of alcoholism, major drug abuse?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "Brian Grazer and I are having an affair.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Anything to chip away at that halo?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "I'm in love with his hair.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Is it going well?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "I was laughing -- you always show the person watching themselves.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "Ben Stiller's latest movie, \"Tower Heist,\" what were you laughing there?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "TILLER: I'm really excited because it's actually a -- it's a genre movie that I've never been in, a heist movie.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "You excited about this one, \"Tower Heist\"?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Oh, wow.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "What's going on with your country?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I -- I'm a -- I'm disappointed that we haven't seen more bold decisions from him and a willingness, I think, to maybe stick to more of what he had, in his campaign, had said in terms of what he was willing to do.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "He disappointed you, Obama?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Are you finding them good -- of comedic value?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I am wary, yes, because I, again --", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Are you wary of discussing this?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "I don't -- I don't see myself as a political commentator or a comedian in any way, though I do enjoy Bill Maher's show.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "-- in your Google hit list?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Well, they are quite funny, some of these Republicans, don't they?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "I think that I can't imagine him being president.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Yes, but when you watch him as a serious presidential candidate, what do you think?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "I mean, I think -- I would think that Mitt Romney would have more of a chance at this point.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "-- your fellow countrymen?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "I saw him on the \"Meet the Press,\" and I was not impressed.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "What about Herman Cain, the pizza guy?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Because he wouldn't answer questions when they started asking about foreign policy, he would just say, \"I'm going to talk to my advisors.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "I just -- I went down there for the first time before the earthquake, and it was in such a bad situation that I wanted to try to do something to help there.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "I mean, why does it still motivate you?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Well, I think everybody's entitled to their opinion.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "What do you feel about people who criticize celebrities for helping the stuff like that, the criticism being you're just doing it to promote yourself?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "You must be sick of it, aren't you?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Sometimes I'm sick of it.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Are you being honest?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Wait a minute.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "-- with the passage of time?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Both.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "I'm affectionate toward the movie or the passage of time in general?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "We're coming to that.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "What do you think of Rick Perry?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Everything he said, I -- you know --", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "What do you think of Herman Cain?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "What's he -- what's he like --", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "I don't know, 11?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "Now it comes out.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Is this true?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Any tantrums?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Endless divorces.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "How have you avoided the cliche Hollywood trap of endless divorces?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "We both sort of come from similar backgrounds as both our parents were...", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "How do -- does one do it?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "Yes, and we -- we both grew up around it in New York and Matthew was successful earlier than I was.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "I just froze up.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "Joe Pesci, he just -- he just freaked me out or something.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "What happened with that?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "He was just good.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Are you good at auditions?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "It's like a nightmare.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "...monstrous box office megastar?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Not that I have found.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "No chink in the armor that we could dwell on?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "You get shot in the head it's over.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "He's kidding, right?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "Die.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Then what you going to do?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "I'm sure there is.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "Is there anybody, do you think, in Hollywood left who's got a better record than that?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Would he beat that?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "Not entirely, because they're not -- they don't have a specific message that they're saying.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "Can you understand it?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Well, Madoff, we did.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "Do you have a -- did you have a character in mind?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "We -- we're on the artist side so we -- (inaudible) table.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "Would you accept that?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "It's hard to understand how it works.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Is Hollywood as ruthless as people say it is?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Put it this way, we developed the movie -- Brian and I developed the movie for several years.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "How -- how -- how important -- let me ask you Brett, how important is someone like Ben to a movie now?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "Yes, a total of six movies.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "Yes, Eddie pitched Brian and I the idea and I've been wanting to work with him since I was a kid, I've been such a big fan, and Brian had done maybe five -- five or six movies with him?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "Ben wasn't -- no, this was after we wrapped the movie.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "Was Ben not available?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "He was, you know, he's kind of -- since I started is right about the time when he started so I've grown up on him.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "What was he like to work with, Matthew?", "qSentId": 732}, {"answer": "Sure...", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "Did you -- did even someone like you feel intimidated?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "...yes, because Eddie has been -- he's iconic for -- for, you know, the last 25 years.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 744, "question": "Working with someone like Eddie?", "qSentId": 743}, {"answer": "Oh my God.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "If you could cast one leading man in the last movie you ever make, who would it be?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "I can name some dead ones.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 797, "question": "Can you name someone?", "qSentId": 796}, {"answer": "I am a big Daniel Day-Lewis fan.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 804, "question": "Who would you say?", "qSentId": 803}, {"answer": "This was in The Freshman.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 830, "question": "This was in The Freshman, right?", "qSentId": 829}, {"answer": "Well, you seem to be getting fed lines.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 833, "question": "And you got in a stage of his career when he was getting fed lines through his ear, right?", "qSentId": 832}, {"answer": "...yes, well, you know, and Ben and Eddie and there are a lot of great ones.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 856, "question": "So he was the best you've seen you think?", "qSentId": 855}, {"answer": "In a movie.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 871, "question": "RAZER: Are you?", "qSentId": 870}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 875, "question": "The Robert Zemeckis movie?", "qSentId": 874}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 877, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 876}, {"answer": "Yes it is.", "docId": "111105pmt", "aSentId": 892, "question": "I think it's going to be a great comeback for Eddie Murphy and you guys, I think you've -- you've -- it's a great (inaudible) film and it's hard, isn't it?", "qSentId": 891}]